technipages.com 2019-08-30

# Privacy Policy - Technipages

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://www.technipages.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

This information may be used to send email notifications to the user when another comment is made. The information may be used for sending a newsletter via email.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

We collect names, email addresses, IP addresses, keep contact form submissions for customer service purposes for 5 years. We do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Affiliate Disclaimer

Some of the products mentioned on this site may include an affiliate link and provide Technipages and its owner(s) and contributes with of monetary earnings. Amazon is an affiliate network we use. When you select a link that goes to Amazon, a cookie may store some data based on your Amazon preferences. You can see Amazon’s privacy notice here [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=asus_gen_not?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496&ld=NSGoogle](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=asus_gen_not?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496&ld=NSGoogle)

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track the number of users on the site, and which posts they view. You can view the Google Analytics privacy policy at <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

## Who we share your data with

We have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, Google, VibrantMedia, and other third-party ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).
  * Users may opt out of other cookies by clicking [here](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/).

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Contact information

Our postal address is  
**7208 W. 65th Street  
Sioux Falls, SD 57106**

We can be reached via e-mail at admin (at) technipages.com

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

We have encrypted the data on this site with SSL for your protection. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

We regularly scan our systems for potential and real data breaches. In the event of a data breach, we will notify our users of the data that was obtained and advise on what action they can take.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries).

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses.
